Guide to the Frederick W. Hilles Manuscript Collection and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Frederick W. Hilles Papers, 1775–1979; Series II; 52.53; 107 boxes + 1 broadside, 1 roll.
  - Research Files, 1900–1975
    - Notes on Subjects, 1924–1975
      - England, general, undated (Box 82, Folder 1266)
        Includes notes on English estates, the perpetual calendar, and English individuals.
      - England, architecture before 1660, undated; 1934–1935 (Box 82, Folder 1267)
      - England, architecture since 1800, undated (Box 82, Folder 1268)
      - Lockhart and Scott, 1939–1949 (Box 83, Folder 1269)
      - Lorraine, Charles and Poussin, undated (Box 83, Folder 1270)
      - Hawthorne, Nathaniel and The Scarlet Letter, undated (Box 83, Folder 1271)
      - Literary, 1924–1973
        - General, 1924–1973 (Box 83, Folder 1272-1273)
        - General, 1924–1973 (Box 83, Folder 1274)
        - Letters, undated (Box 83, Folder 1275)
          Includes letters by Johnson, Coleridge, and Reynolds.
        - Novels, undated (Box 83, Folder 1276)
        - Johnson and his circle, 1937–1971 (Box 83, Folder 1277)
          Includes notes on Samuel Johnson, Joshua Reynolds, and others. Many notes are written on the verso of Yale documents and personal papers.
        - Johnson and his circle, 1937–1971 (Box 84, Folder 1278-1279)
        - Pope, Alexander, undated (Box 84, Folder 1280-1282)
          Includes excerpts from Horace Walpole, Lord Byron, and John Ruskin pertaining to Pope.
        - Presses and libraries, undated (Box 84, Folder 1283-1284)
          Includes manuscript and printed material pertaining to or created by presses and libraries.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, 1937–1975
        - General, undated (Box 84, Folder 1285-1287)
        - General, undated (Box 85, Folder 1288-1292)
        - Research scrapbook, undated (Box 142, Folder 1771)
        - Research scrapbook, undated (Box 143, Folder 1772)
        - Copies of documents, undated (Box 85, Folder 1293)
        - Reynolds and James Boswell, undated (Box 85, Folder 1294-1295)
          Includes notes on Reynolds, notes on Boswell, and copies of letters between Reynolds and Boswell.
        - Reynolds and Horace Walpole, 1950–1975 (Box 86, Folder 1296)
        - Reynolds, William Hazlitt, and Benjamin Hayden, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 1297)
      - Yale University Library, 1959–1973 (Box 86, Folder 1298)
        Includes catalog cards, circulation cards, and rules for use of the Boswell Papers.
      - Yale University Press, 1937–1961 (Box 86, Folder 1299)
        Includes pamphlets, order forms, ephemera, and rules of governance for the press.
    - Notes on Manuscripts, 1925–1966
      - Burke, Edmund, list of letters, undated (Box 86, Folder 1300)
      - Chambers, Robert and Ann, lists of manuscripts, undated (Box 86, Folder 1301-1302)
        Also includes notes about manuscripts.
      - Chesterfield, Philip Dormer Stanhope, undated (Box 86, Folder 1303)
      - Correspondence with dealers, 1925–1966 (Box 86, Folder 1304)
      - Correspondence related materials regarding dealers, 1952; undated (Box 86, Folder 1305)
      - Froude, James Anthony, notes on manuscripts, undated (Box 86, Folder 1306)
      - Johnson, William, notes on manuscripts, undated (Box 86, Folder 1307)
      - Northcote, James, lists of manuscripts, undated (Box 86, Folder 1308)
      - Précis of correspondence not in the Frederick W. Hilles collection, undated (Box 86, Folder 1309)
      - Unidentified notes, undated (Box 86, Folder 1310-1311)
    - Reproductions
      Photocopies of original documents and letters, as well as photocopies of reference sources.
      - Annals of the Fine Arts, undated (Box 87, Folder 1312)
      - Arblay, Frances (Burney) d' (Box 87, Folder 1313)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Charles Burney, 1797.
      - Arblay, Frances (Burney) d' (Box 87, Folder 1314)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Charles Burney, 1800.
      - Carlyle, Thomas (Box 87, Folder 1315)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Robert Browning, 1856.
      - Carlyle, Thomas (Box 87, Folder 1316)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to John Carlyle, 1835.
      - Chambers, Sir William (Box 87, Folder 1317)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Sir Joshua Reynolds, 1771?, 1 page, with address.
      - Chambers, Sir William (Box 87, Folder 1318)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Sir Joshua Reynolds, 1790 October 18, London, 2 pages, with address.
      - Daschkov, Princess of (Box 87, Folder 1319)
        Autograph letter, signed (photocopy).
      - Humphry, Ozias (Box 87, Folder 1320)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Sir Joshua Reynolds, 1781 Dec 21, 1 page.
      - Johnson, Elizabeth, undated (Box 87, Folder 1321)
        Photocopy of The Explication of the Vision to Ezekiel
      - Johnson, Samuel (Box 87, Folder 1322)
        Photocopy of a copy of The Life of Pope in the hand of Mrs. Thrale.
      - Johnson, Samuel (Box 87, Folder 1323)
        Photocopies of letters.
      - Johnson, Samuel (Box 141, Folder 1763)
        Binder of reproductions related to Johnson.
      - Johnson, Samuel (Box 141, Folder 1764)
        Binder of reproductions of manuscript and proof sheets for Johnson's Life of Pope.
      - Malone, Edward (Box 87, Folder 1324)
        Photocopies of letters to Edmund Burke.
      - Mill, John Stuart (Box 87, Folder 1325)
        Photocopies of three letters to Thomas Carlyle.
      - More, Hannah (Box 87, Folder 1326)
        Photocopies of letters to Frances Reynolds.
      - Northcote, James (Box 87, Folder 1327)
        Photocopy of a fragment of a letter to an unidentified recipient, 1771 July 21.
      - Northcote, James (Box 87, Folder 1328)
        Photocopies of two letters to his brother, 1776.
      - Palmer, Mary, undated (Box 87, Folder 1329-1330)
        Reproductions of letters.
      - Reynolds, Frances (Box 87, Folder 1331)
        Autograph letter, signed, (positive photostat) to Elizabeth Montagu, 1785 Jul 12, Richmond, 4 pages.
      - Reynolds, Frances (Box 88, Folder 1332)
        Photocopies of assorted poems.
      - Reynolds, Frances (Box 88, Folder 1333)
        Photocopies of notes on Johnson.
      - Reynolds, Frances (Box 88, Folder 1334)
        Photocopies of commonplace book.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1335)
        Autograph letter (photostat) to Elizabeth Montagu, 1773 March or April, 1 page, with address.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1336)
        Five autograph letters, signed, (photostats) to Edmund Burke, 1768-1791.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1337)
        Four autograph letters, signed (photocopies), to Thomas Robinson, 2nd Baron Grantham, 1772-1777.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1338)
        Autograph letter (in the 3rd person; photostat) to Thomas Cadell, 1791 April 18, regarding the Johnson monument.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1339)
        Autograph letter, signed (photocopy), to Dr. Farr, 1775 November 23, London, 1 page.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1340)
        Statement (negative photostat) in the hand of Mary Palmer regarding the picture from Macbeth commissioned by John Boydell, 1791 December.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1341)
        Autograph letter, signed (photocopy), to Anne Liddell Fitzroy Fitzpatrick, Lady Ossory, 1791 January 3. Accompanied by another photocopy.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1342)
        Autograph letter, signed (photocopy), to John Fitzpatrick, second Earl of Upper Ossory, 1788 October 2.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1343)
        Four autograph letters, signed (negative photostats), to Sir William Forbes, 1778-1783.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1344)
        Autograph letter, signed (negative photostat), to Elizabeth Humphry, 1765 April 30, London, 1 page.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1345)
        Autograph letter, signed (negative photostat), to Bennett Langton, 1782 September 12, London, 3 pages.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1346)
        Autograph letter, signed (photocopy), to Charlotte Lennox, 1776 October 9.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1347)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Charlotte Lennox, 1775 January 18, London, 1 page, with mathematical calculations on page 4.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1348)
        Two autograph letters, signed (photocopies), to Giuseppe Pelli, 1776.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1349)
        Three autograph letters, signed (positive photostats), to Thomas Morrison, 1766-1771. Accompanied by Morrison's A Pindaric Ode on Painting (1767), Los Angeles, 1952.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1350)
        Letter (in the third person, in the hand of Frances Reynolds; negative photostat), to Thomas and Anne Percy, undated.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1351)
        Four autograph letters (in the 3rd person; photocopies) to Mr. Radcliffe.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1352)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Lord Salisbury, 1788 February 11.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1353)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Jonathan Shipley, 1784 September 25, London.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1354)
        Autograph letter, signed, (negative photostat) Andrew Strahan, 1785 October 23, London, 2 pages.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1355)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Andrew Strahan, 1788 June 1.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1356)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Prince Gregory Alexandrovitch Potemkin, 1789 August 4, London, 3 pages, with a fourth page titled: "Sujet de tableau de S: M: impériale."
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1357)
        Autograph letter, signed, (positive photostat) to Count Simon Vorontzov, 1790 May 25, London, 2 pages.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1358)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Benjamin West, 1789 April 7, London, 2 pages.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1359)
        Autograph letter, signed, (photocopy) to Miss Weston, 1751 April 30, Rome, 2 pages, with address.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1360)
        Letter to Sir William Chambers, 1775 January 28, with related material.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1361-1363)
        Photocopies pertaining to the estate of Joshua Reynolds.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 88, Folder 1364-1365)
        Transcripts of Reynolds' engagement book.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 89, Folder 1366-1367)
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 89, Folder 1368-1369)
        Transcripts of Reynolds' manuscripts and commonplace book.
      - Reynolds, Sir Joshua (Box 89, Folder 1370-1371)
        Assorted Reynolds reproductions.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 89, Folder 1372)
        Photographs of a 1781 notebook and photographs of a 1785 notebook held at the Royal Academy.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 90, Folder 1373)
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 136, Folder 1748-1749)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1757-1758 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 136, Folder 1750-1751)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1759-1760 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 137, Folder 1752-1753)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1761-1762 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 137, Folder 1754-1755)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1764-1765 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 138, Folder 1756)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1766-1768 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 139, Folder 1759)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1769-1770 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 139, Folder 1760)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1771-1772 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 138, Folder 1757)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1773, 1777, and 1779 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 138, Folder 1758)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1782-1784 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 140, Folder 1762)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1786-1787 and 1789-1790 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 139, Folder 1761)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' 1788 pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 141, Folder 1765)
        Reproductions of Reynolds' undated pocketbooks.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 141, Folder 1766)
        Reproductions of Joshua Reynolds' 1752 Florence sketchbook.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 141, Folder 1767)
        Reproductions of Joshua Reynolds' 1752 Venice sketchbook.
      - Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 141, Folder 1768)
        Binder of correspondence with the Huntington Library and reproductions of Reynolds letters at the Huntington.
      - Richardson, Samuel (Box 90, Folder 1374)
        Autograph letter, signed (photocopy), to Mrs. Watts, 1756 May 13.
      - Siries, Luigi (Box 90, Folder 1375)
        Photocopy of letter to Raimondo Cocchi, 1773 December 31, with notes by Frederick W. Hilles.
      - Scott, Sir Walter (Box 90, Folder 1376)
      - Vorontsov, Count Semen Romanovich (Box 90, Folder 1377)
        Photocopies of four autograph letters (in the 3rd person) and one autograph letter, signed, to Edmund Burke, 1791-1793.
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 90, Folder 1378-1380)
        Photocopies.
      - Museum reproductions, undated (Box 90, Folder 1381)
        Black and white reproductions of museum artworks on cards.
      - Museum reproductions, undated (Box 91, Folder 1382-1430)
        Color reproductions of museum works on paper.
        Conditions Governing Access
        needs new 11x17 box
      - Museum reproductions, undated (Box 92, Folder 1431-1476)
      - Museum reproductions, undated; 4 (Box 146 (Oversize), Folder 1781-1784)
        Black and white and color reproductions of museum works on paper and linen.
      - Museum reproductions, undated; 4 (Box 149 (Roll), Folder 1791)
      - Microfilm, undated (Box 144)
        Microfilm related to Reynolds and Johnson.
    - Card Catalogs
      Arranged in the order received by the library.
      - Subject files, undated (Box 93)
        Includes subject files on Reynolds, Montesquieu, Shakespeare, Johnson, and others.
      - Subject files, undated (Box 94)
  - Teaching Material, 1913–1976
    Organized under three headings: Yale University, Temple University, and Westminster School.
    - Yale University, 1913–1976
      Organized under three headings: Class Notes, Subject Files, and Administrative Files.
      - Class Notes, 1913–1963
        - The Age of Johnson, 1937–1965 (Box 95, Folder 1477-1481)
          Material for English 44b.
        - The Age of Pope, 1940–1942 (Box 95, Folder 1482-1484)
        - Chaucer, 1913–1963 (Box 95, Folder 1485)
        - Chaucer, 1913–1963 (Box 96, Folder 1486)
        - History of Arts and Letters, 1935 (Box 96, Folder 1487-1501)
        - Eighteenth Century Literature, 1932 (Box 97, Folder 1502)
        - English Biographers, 1938–1957 (Box 97, Folder 1503-1507)
        - English Literature, Freshman, undated (Box 97, Folder 1508)
        - English Literature, Sophomore, 1931–1939 (Box 97, Folder 1509-1512)
          Material for term examinations, tests on Milton, and the spring and fall reading periods of English 20.
        - English Literature, Sophomore, 1931–1939 (Box 98, Folder 1513)
        - Literary Interpretation and Analysis, 1942–1962 (Box 98, Folder 1514-1515)
          Examinations for English 10, 15, and 15a.
        - Readings in English Literature, 1947–1948 (Box 98, Folder 1516)
        - Assorted courses, 1915–1961 (Box 98, Folder 1517-1519)
          Includes examinations for assorted English Literature courses, including the Age of Johnson, the Age of Pope, Freshman English, and a course on Shakespeare.
        - Assorted courses, 1915–1961 (Box 99, Folder 1520-1524)
        - Assorted courses, 1915–1961 (Box 100, Folder 1525-1530)
        - Assorted courses, 1915–1961 (Box 101, Folder 1531-1533)
        - Language tests, undated (Box 101, Folder 1534)
      - Subject Files, 1925–1967
        - Bacon, Francis, 1938; undated (Box 101, Folder 1535)
        - Blake, William, 1948 (Box 101, Folder 1536)
        - Burke, Edmund, Gibbon, Edward, and Reynolds, Joshua, undated (Box 101, Folder 1537)
        - Burns, Robert, 1956; undated (Box 101, Folder 1538)
        - Byron, George Gordon, 1935–1939; undated (Box 101, Folder 1539)
        - Cowper, William, undated (Box 101, Folder 1540)
          Includes an engraved portrait of Cowper.
        - Crime and Punishment, 1948–1962 (Box 101, Folder 1541)
        - Fielding, Henry, 1941–1967 (Box 102, Folder 1542-1543)
        - Goldsmith, Oliver, 1942–1964 (Box 102, Folder 1544)
        - Gray, Thomas, undated (Box 102, Folder 1545)
        - Malory, Thomas, undated (Box 102, Folder 1546)
        - Milton, John, 1938–1942; undated (Box 102, Folder 1547)
        - Richardson, Samuel, 1960; undated (Box 102, Folder 1548)
        - Sheridan, Richard Brinsley, undated (Box 102, Folder 1549)
        - Smart, Christopher and Chatterton, Thomas, undated (Box 102, Folder 1550)
        - Smollett, Tobias, 1925–1940 (Box 102, Folder 1551)
        - Spenser, Edmund, 1929–1939; undated (Box 103, Folder 1552)
        - Sterne, Laurence, undated (Box 103, Folder 1553)
        - Swift, Jonathan, 1956; undated (Box 103, Folder 1554-1555)
        - Thomson, James, and Collins, William, undated (Box 103, Folder 1556)
        - Assorted notes, undated (Box 103, Folder 1557)
      - Administrative Files, 1941–1976
        - Bodman Fund, 1955–1962 (Box 103, Folder 1558)
        - Campaign for Yale, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 1559)
        - Committee on the Humanities, 1967 (Box 103, Folder 1560)
          Includes material on fellowships and academic indifference at Yale.
        - Committees of Yale University Library, 1962–1963 (Box 103, Folder 1561)
        - Donations to Yale University, 1966–1974 (Box 103, Folder 1562)
        - Foundation for Youth, 1962–1966 (Box 103, Folder 1563)
        - Morse Fellowship, 1956–1967 (Box 103, Folder 1564)
        - Teaching resources, 1941; 1970 (Box 104, Folder 1565-1566)
          Includes manuals on teaching and writing style.
        - University communications, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 1567-1568)
          Includes material on the Black Panther trials, the Vinland Map, the Ezra Pound Center, and University events.
        - University communications, 1959 (Box 147 (Oversize), Folder 1785)
          Announcement for Frederick W. Hilles lecture on Rasselas.
        - University statements and publications, 1946–1967 (Box 104, Folder 1569-1570)
        - Yale University Council, 1974–1975 (Box 104, Folder 1571)
        - Yale University Press, 1959–1976 (Box 105, Folder 1572-1573)
    - Temple University, 1973–1975
      Administrative files from Frederick W. Hilles' tenure at Temple University.
      - Faculty handbook, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 1574)
      - Doctoral program in English report, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 1575)
      - Agreement between Temple University and the American Association of University Professors, Temple Chapter, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 1576)
      - Graduate School bulletin, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 1577)
    - Westminster School, 1962–1964
      - Administrative files, 1962–1964 (Box 106, Folder 1578)
  - Personal and Family Papers, 1775–1976
    - Correspondence, 1940–1973
      - C. D. and Elisabeth Hilles, 1940–1945 (Box 106, Folder 1579-1581)
        Includes correspondence between C. D. Hilles, Elisabeth Hilles, and associates. Also includes negatives and photographs.
      - C. D. Hilles, 1940–1942 (Box 107, Folder 1582-1584)
      - Frederick W. Hilles, 1919–1973 (Box 107, Folder 1585-1587)
        Includes a birthday card, correspondence regarding the Morse Fellowship, and correspondence regarding the gift of C. D. Hilles' papers to the Yale Library.
      - Frederick W. and Susan Morse Hilles, 1915–1972 (Box 107, Folder 1588-1590)
        Includes correspondence among F. W. Hilles, Susan Morse Hilles, family members, and associates.
      - Morse family, 1879; 1898 (Box 107, Folder 1591)
    - Financial and Personal Records, 1775–1965
      Organized under three headings: C. D. Hilles, Elizabeth Lee and Samuel Hilles, and Frederick W. and Susan Morse Hilles.
      - C. D. Hilles, 1877–1932
        Arranged alphabetically by type of material.
        - Account and check books, 1901–1909 (Box 108, Folder 1592)
          Includes records for the activities of C. D. and Samuel Hilles.
        - Autograph book, 1885–1890 (Box 108, Folder 1593)
        - Financial notebook, 1896–1900 (Box 108, Folder 1594)
          Notebook documenting C. D. Hilles' personal expenditures.
        - Invitations and calling cards, 1877–1912 (Box 108, Folder 1595-1599)
        - National Republican Club addresses to C. D. Hilles, 1922 (Box 109, Folder 1600)
          Photocopied publication.
        - Republication National Convention scrapbook, 1932 (Box 109, Folder 1601)
        - Receipts, 1899–1905 (Box 109, Folder 1602-1606)
          Receipts documenting C. D. Hilles' personal expenditures and tenure as superintendent of the New York Juvenile Asylum and secretary and steward of the Boys Industrial School, Fairfield County, Connecticut.
      - Elizabeth Lee and Samuel Hilles, 1775–1909
        - Bank filing book (Box 110, Folder 1607)
          Empty.
        - Receipts, 1904 (Box 110, Folder 1608)
          Includes mortgages, maps, and other documents pertaining to property owned by the Hilles family in Barnesville, Ohio.
        - Receipts, 1904 (Box 147 (Oversize), Folder 1231)
        - Personal and financial records, 1775–1909 (Box 110, Folder 1609-1611)
          Includes documentation of Samuel Hilles' financial expenditures and involvement in fraternal organizations, and Southern, Revolutionary, and Confederate currency.
      - Frederick W. and Susan Morse Hilles, 1917–1976
        - Academic records, 1920–1922 (Box 110, Folder 1612-1613)
          Includes unidentified class notes and class notes for the Age of Johnson.
        - Agency account, 1944–1956 (Box 110, Folder 1614)
          Contains documentation on Frederick W. Hilles' financial agency account.
        - Bank books and statements, 1959–1961 (Box 111, Folder 1615-1616)
        - Bank books and statements, 1959–1961 (Box 111, Folder 1617-1618)
        - Bookplate (Frederick W. Hilles), undated (Box 111, Folder 1619)
          Sketches and proofs for F. W. Hilles bookplate
        - Bills and receipts, 1940–1958 (Box 111, Folder 1620)
        - Bills and receipts, 1941–1958 (Box 112, Folder 1621-1625)
        - Bills and receipts, 1946–1960 (Box 113, Folder 1626-1629)
        - Bills, Susan Morse Hilles, 1940–1949 (Box 113, Folder 1630)
        - Bills, Susan Morse Hilles, 1940–1949 (Box 114, Folder 1631-1632)
        - Donation acknowledgments, 1938–1975 (Box 114, Folder 1633)
        - Genealogy book, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 1634)
        - Income tax, 1947–1960 (Box 114)
          Includes SSNs; SHRED?
        - International travel, 1953–1963 (Box 115, Folder 1635-1636)
        - Memberships, 1917–1976 (Box 115, Folder 1637)
          Ephemera and correspondence regarding Frederick W. Hilles' membership in organizations.
        - Memorial services, 1963–1975 (Box 115, Folder 1638)
        - Pansy Patch Farm, 1951–1953 (Box 115, Folder 1639)
          Includes material on the management of Pansy Patch Farm, Paradise, Nova Scotia.
        - Pansy Patch Farm, 1951–1953 (Box 116, Folder 1640-1641)